(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T04:49:00.405427",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
アンデッドアリスへ
To Undead Alice,
「思うように逝けないなら 私を吸って 君は生きて」
"If you can't pass away as you wish, feed on me and live on."
狂ってた 君の残響は 僕じゃなくたって聴こえるのに
You went mad, and your echoes are audible even if it's not me.
自傷案を募るたび 幸せ吸って毒を吐いて
Every time I invite self-harm, I breathe in happiness and spit poison.
理想 ジャンキー 二人だけが 正常なんて気持ちいいじゃんか
Ideal junkies, isn't it nice that only the two of us are normal?
会いたいが歪文化したい 病が 会えなくて溢れ出すローが
Wanting to see you, the sickness of distorted love overflowing because I can't see you...
仲良くなっちゃってやっぱつらいや
We got close, and as expected, it hurts.
ドキドキが嫌になって 僕が君を殺す前に 死んでくれ
Before heartbeats annoy me and I kill you, just die for me.
ズルしていいよ ズルくていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly.
壊していいよ 怖くていいよ
It's okay to break it, it's okay to be scared.
卑俗な愛は ここに埋めよう 忘れるんだ こんなのもやめよう
Let's bury this base love here, forget it, let's stop this already.
嫌ったほうが気楽でいい でも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
It's easier to hate, but isn't it better that you weigh heavy on my mind?
もう笑えない 僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile.
予想通り 僕の夢が 輝くほど 君は陰っていく
As expected, the more my dreams shine, the more you grow dim.
犠牲を我慢と呼んで 汚れた手で撫で回した
Calling sacrifice endurance, I fondled you with dirty hands.
悪ようなしないように それがつまり悪い形
So as not to act evil—which in turn is an evil shape—
保存 状態 愛は冷凍 で 何度も聞いた 「あたためますか?」
state of preservation, love is frozen, I've heard it many times: "Would you like that warmed up?"
正しくありたい本能が 正しくないことの脂肪が 仲良くなっちゃってやっぱつらいや
The instinct to be righteous, the fat of unrighteousness—we got close, and as expected, it hurts.
ドキドキが嫌になって 僕が君を殺す前に 死んでやる
Before heartbeats annoy me and I kill you, I'll die for you.
ズルしていいよ ズルくていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly.
壊していいよ 怖くていいよ
It's okay to break it, it's okay to be scared.
卑俗な愛は ここに埋めよう 忘れるんだ こんなのもやめよう
Let's bury this base love here, forget it, let's stop this already.
嫌ったほうが気楽でいい でも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
It's easier to hate, but isn't it better that you weigh heavy on my mind?
もう笑えない 僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile.
ずっとこのまま ふたりで夢を見れるって
That we could keep dreaming together just like this...
勝手ばかりで 君はどんな顔で笑っていたっけ
Always acting on your own, what kind of face were you smiling with?
バイバイしたから 元通りなんて幻想だ
Since we said bye-bye, thinking things are back to normal is an illusion.
まあまあツライじゃん 胸を割いて愛を潰してくれよ
Well, it's pretty painful—slice open my chest and crush this love.
ズルしていいよ ズルくていいよ
It's okay to cheat, it's okay to be sly.
壊していいよ 怖くていいよ
It's okay to break it, it's okay to be scared.
卑俗な愛は ここに埋めよう 忘れるんだ こんなのもやめよう
Let's bury this base love here, forget it, let's stop this already.
嫌ったほうが気楽でいい でも想ったほうが重くていいじゃんか
It's easier to hate, but isn't it better that you weigh heavy on my mind?
もう笑えない 僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile.
痛いぐらいじゃ逝きそうもないや
Just being in pain won't make me pass away.
時効ぐらいじゃ消えそうもないや
Just the statute of limitations won't make me disappear.
ごめんねなんて言えるはずない
There's no way I could ever say "I'm sorry."
「いつかきっと なんとか笑える」なんて 間違いじゃないか 違うじゃないか
"Surely one day we'll somehow be able to smile"—isn't that a mistake? Isn't that wrong?
死ねない想いは 希望か絶望か
Is this inability to die a hope or a despair?
もう笑えない 僕の アンデッドアリスへ
To my Undead Alice who can no longer smile.
見ていってください！
Check it out!
着いた。
We've arrived.
めっちゃ一人で……、でっけぇ。
All by myself... It's huge.
あ、鳩いる。待って。
Ah, there are pigeons. Wait.
あ…ちょっと、待っている。
Ah... wait, they're waiting.
涼しい。
It's cool.
ねえ、涼しいね。
Hey, it's cool, isn't it?
この前さ。
Just the other day...
涼しい。
It's cool.
ここに来た。
I've come here.
何食べよっかな。
What should I eat?
何食べる？
What should I get?
あ、がっつりね、ん、これハンバーグや。
Ah, something hearty... hm, a hamburger steak.
絶対ハンバーグにしよ。
I'm definitely getting the hamburger steak.
来た！
It's here!
え、めっちゃ美味しそう。
Whoa, it looks so good.
何これ？
What is this?
めっちゃ美味しそう。何頼んだんだろ？
It looks so good. What did I order?
めっちゃ健康に良さそう。
It looks super healthy.
いいね。
Nice.
食べよ？
Shall we eat?
食べた！
I ate!
美味しかった。
It was delicious.
食べた？
Did you eat?
でっか！
Huge!
あ、私ここ食べる。このお餅、あとイチゴ。
Ah, I'll eat this part. These rice cakes, and the strawberry.
半分こしよ。
Let's share it.
お腹いっぱい。めっちゃお腹いっぱい。
I'm full. So full.
食べた。
I ate.
よかった、食べたね。
Good thing I ate.
あ、もう無理。
Ah, I can't eat anymore.
鯉、
Koi...
こっち見て。
Look over here.
鯉。
Koi.
消えちゃいそう。
It's about to disappear.
鳥。
Bird.
何して…
What are...
何してるの？
What are you doing?
鳥。
Bird.
あ。
Ah.
魚だ。
It's a fish.
日が沈むのって時間かかるよね。
Sunsets take a long time to set, don't they?
まだ眠ってないの？
Aren't you sleepy yet?
もう沈んだやろ、これ。ほぼ。
It's probably already set. Almost.
ほぼ沈んだね。
Almost set, yeah.
わ。
Wow.
石を感じる。
I can feel the stone.
お風呂だ。
It's a bath!
It's a bath.
外にもお風呂だ。
There's a bath outside too.
すごい。
Awesome.
あ、タワー。
Ah, the tower.
すごい。
Amazing.
トイレ！
Toilet!
ベッド！
Bed!
足が生えてまいりました。
Legs have sprouted.
何頼んだの？
What did you order?
極上すぎ！
Too luxurious!
これ、あれね、日本酒。
This is, you know, sake.
飲んでみたい。
I want to try drinking it.
口頂戴。
Let me have a taste.
うわ
Whoa!
アルコールなし
Alcohol-free!
え、なんか… 高そう。何これ？
Huh, wow... looks expensive. What is this?
季節の… 先付け3種
Seasonal... three appetizers.
どれが3種なんだ？
Which ones are the three?
うわ、肉きた！
Whoa, meat!
とろけそう…
It looks like it'll melt...
わさび。
Wasabi.
食べます！
I'll dig in!
ごちそうた。
Thanks for the meal.
美味しかったけど、冷たかった…
It was good, but cold...
お腹いっぱいだね。
I'm so full.
眠い。
I'm sleepy.
おはよー！
Good morning!
起きて！
Wake up!
めっちゃ美味しそう！あー、食べたい！
This looks so good! Ah, I wanna eat!
食べていい？
Can I eat?
ごちそうさまでした。
Thank you for the meal.
お腹いっぱい！
I'm stuffed!
これ… ホテルに合ってたやつ！これ絶対欲しかったんだ。
This... was the one at the hotel!
I totally wanted this.
これ昨日飲んでて美味しかったじゃん。買うか。
This was good when I drank it yesterday.
I'll buy it.
やばい！何も用意してない！荷造りも！何も用意してない！
Oh no! I haven't prepared anything!
Packing too! I haven't prepared anything!
おい！手伝えお前！もう終わり終わったの？
Hey! Help me out, you!
Are you already done?
たとえば今 君が その瞳濡らしていたとしても
Even if right now your eyes were moist with tears,
呼ぶ声は もう 聞こえない
I can no longer hear your voice calling out.
絵の具を溶かすように
Like dissolving paint,
君との日々は 記憶の中滲んでく
our days together blur deep within memories.
何かを求めれば 何かが
Whenever I wish for something,
こぼれ落ちてく そんな この世界で
something else spills over in this world.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like the flower waiting for the spring wind,
君という光があるのなら
if there is a light called you,
巡り巡る運命を超えて 咲かせるさ 愛の花を 花束を
I'll transcend the revolving fate to bloom the flower and bouquet of love.
願いが叶うなら ふたりの世界 また生きてみたい
If my wish comes true, I want to live in our world once more.
あのキスから芽吹く日々は
The days budding from that kiss—
水色花びらはもう香りを忘れ
the aqua petals have already forgotten their scent,
君への想い枯れてゆく
and my feelings for you are withering away.
散ってしまいそうな心に覚えたての愛の美しさを ねぇ 咲かせて
Take my heart before it scatters and make the newly remembered beauty of love bloom.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like the flower waiting for the spring wind,
飾りない心で いられたら
if I could remain with an unadorned heart,
触れられなくても 想い煩っても 忘れないよ
even without touching, even if I struggle with longing, I will never forget.
春の風を待つ あの花のように
Like the flower waiting for the spring wind,
飾らない 心でいられたら
if I could remain with an unadorned heart,
触れられなくても 想い煩っても 忘れないよ
even without touching, even if I struggle with longing, I will never forget.
この恋をひとつずつ束ねていて
Bundling this love one by one,
君という光があるのなら
if there is a light called you,
巡り巡る運命を超えて 咲かせるさ 愛の花を 花束を
I'll transcend the revolving fate to bloom the flower and bouquet of love.
目指せ100万円！ホロライブ激辛王決定戦！
Aim for 1 million yen! Hololive Super Spicy King Deciding Match!
司会は私、holXの女幹部 鷹嶺ルイがね、お送りさせていただきます
I am the host, holoX's female executive Takane Lui, presenting this to you.
今日、100万円を目指して激辛を喰らう 猛者たちがここに集まっていただきました
Today, fierce competitors aiming for 1 million yen while eating super spicy food have gathered here.
一人ずつ自己紹介してもらいましょうか
Shall we have them introduce themselves one by one?
ワーカホリックにスパイスは必須！ということでホロライブスタッフの友人Aです よろしくお願いしまーす
Spice is a must for a workaholic! With that said, I'm hololive staff A-san. Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いします
Please treat us well!
いぇーい
Yay!
100万円食べます
I'll eat 1 million yen worth!
ラプラス・ダークネスです
I'm Laplus Darknesss.
よろしく〜
Nice to meet you~!
辛味と寝ました。白上フブキです。よろしくお願いします
I slept with spiciness. I'm Shirakami Fubuki. Nice to meet you.
ここ辛味でーす
This is spiciness right here!
ガチ恋泣くぞ！
Hardcore fans are gonna cry!
好きなカレーは子供用のバターチキンだ…
My favorite curry is child-friendly butter chicken...
でも麦ジュースがあれば何とか解決できる！ってエロい人も言ってる。
But 'barley juice' can solve anything! Or so some lewd person says.
頑張ります！
I'll do my best!
なんか不思議なメンバーが集まりましたが…え、ラプラスなんでこの4人になったの？
Somehow a mysterious member gathering happened... Eh, Laplus, why did it become these four?
そうだ、確かに
True, come to think of it.
なんか、フブキさんとえーちゃんさんは辛いの好きなの知ってるけど、なんか面白そうだなと思って呼んで…
Well, I know Fubuki-san and A-chan like spicy food, but I thought it'd be interesting so I invited them...
で、アキロゼさんは雑魚だけど…
And Akirose-san is a scrub, but...
おいおいお前！雑魚って言ったな！お前も雑魚だろうが！
Hey hey, you! You called me a scrub! You're a scrub too!
なんかいい勝負できそうだなと思って
...I thought we could have a good match.
なるほど、なるほどね。足の引っ張り合いが始まるんだ
I see, I see. A mutual dragging-down begins.
絶対負けない！
I'll never lose!
100万円はラプちゃんからの…holoXからの資金ということですね？
100 million yen is Lap-chan's... I mean, funding from holoX, right?
まあそれはね、あの…もらってからのお楽しみだよね。
Well, that's, um... something to look forward to after receiving it.
いやー楽しみだなー！
Man, I'm looking forward to it!
holoXからのポケットマネーで食う飯はうまいぞー！
Eating meals with holoX's pocket money is delicious!
ルイ、よろしく！
Lui, please!
ということでね、この4人の熱い勇士と戦う料理をご紹介しましょう。
And so, let's introduce these four passionate fighters and the battle dishes.
来い！ルイ
Come on, Lui!
はい
Yes.
ちょっとね、なんか、すごい、結構辛そう。そう辛いんだよね。ちょっとね、皆さんにはお見せできないのが残念なくらい本当に辛そうなんですけれども…
Well, it looks pretty spicy. It really is spicy. It's almost a shame we can't show it to everyone, it looks genuinely spicy...
比較のために辛くないものも用意していただいたので、辛くない方からちょっと食べてみましょう。
...but since we also prepared a non-spicy one for comparison, let's try the non-spicy one first.
はい、じゃあルイ、あーん
Okay, then Lui, say aah.
あーん、んー！
Aah... Mm!
あーいいですね、かわいいかわいい
Ah, nice, cute, cute.
で、こっちが辛い方らしい。辛いやつ、あーなんか赤いな…
And, this one seems to be the spicy one. The spicy one... Ah, it looks kind of red...
いただきます
Itadakimasu.
ん？変わんない？
Hm? Doesn't change?
うそー！！
No way!!
違っ！私匂いで分かるけど、明らかに おかしいんだよねこっち。
Wait! I can tell by the smell, this one is clearly weird.
企画倒れになっちゃうからおなじだったら！お前バケモンだよバケモン。
If they're the same, the segment flops! You're a monster, a monster.
そんなはずない！そんなはずない！全然辛くないんだけど。
No way! No way! It's not spicy at all.
头おかしいだろ！みんな大丈夫だと思います。
You're out of your mind! I think everyone will be fine.
なのでね、私のちょっと、あの味覚を信じて頑張って食べていってくださいね。誰も信じられないけどね！
So, please trust my, um, sense of taste and do your best to eat it! Though nobody can trust you!
信じられるのかな？まだ手元に来てないからわかんないんだけどね。
Can we trust it? We don't know since it hasn't reached us yet.
はい、ということで、商品説明もね、終わったところで対戦に参りましょう！皆様、準備はいいですか？
Yes, and with the product explanation finished, let's proceed to the match! Everyone, are you ready?
いくぞー！食わせろ！
Let's go! Feed us!
はい、実はこの中に1人だけ辛くないものが配られています。皆さん、誰が辛くないの食べてるか考えてみてくださいね。
Yes, actually, only one person has been given a non-spicy dish. Everyone, please try to guess who is eating the non-spicy one.
運ばれてきました〜
It has been delivered~
なるほど？どうですかね皆さん。印象はどうですか？
I see? What do you think, everyone? What's your impression?
いや、めちゃめちゃ普通に辛そう。あの、ドロドロしてますね。
Man, it looks ridiculously spicy. Um, it's thick and sludge-like.
やばい、なんかもう目が…「見ちゃダメ！」って言ってる
Oh no, my eyes are already saying 'Don't look!'
あーすごいでも…あー！やばい！めちゃめちゃいい匂いする！
Ah, amazing though... Ah! Oh no! It smells amazing!
目が痛い！目が痛い！
My eyes hurt! My eyes hurt!
はい、ということで、皆さんのところにね、商品が揃ったところで早速、食べてもらいましょう！
Yes, and now that the products have reached everyone, let's have you eat them right away!
激辛選手権、スタート！
Super Spicy Championship, start!
えーちゃんから、食べていただきましょう。
Let's have A-chan eat first.
さっさと食えよ！辛そうですよ、これはちょっと
Eat already! This looks spicy, this is a bit...
でも全然大丈夫だからね、辛いの
But it's totally fine, the spicy part...
あ、ほんですか？あーん…どうかな？んー、美味しい！？
Ah, really? Aah... How is it? Mhm, delicious!?
美味しい！ちゃんと辛みもあって、なんというか、ちょっと濃いめのお辛さとマッチして、ご飯食べたくなりますね。
Delicious! It has proper spiciness, and somehow matches the rich spiciness, making you want to eat rice.
あー、確かに。ご飯食べたくなるところだわ。じゃあ続いて…
Ah, true. It's the kind that makes you want rice. Well then, next...
辛いのが苦手なラプちゃん行ってみようか。
Let's have Lap-chan, who is bad with spicy food, try it.
バケモノ2が隣にいるからさ、ちょっと…大丈夫大丈夫！私を信じて
Since monster 2 is next to me, just... It's fine, fine! Trust me.
お前が一番信じられないよ。辛い物の場合は一番信じられない
You're the last person I can trust. Especially when it comes to spicy food.
いただきます
Itadakimasu.
あ、やばい！うわあああ！あつ！痛い！痛い痛い！口に入れたとたん痛いね。やばい！牛乳牛乳！
Ah, no! Uwaaaah! Hot! It hurts! It hurts so much! The moment I put it in my mouth, it hurts. Oh no! Milk, milk!
放送事故！放送事故！お披露目でそれはまずい！吐かれる前にちょっと、フブキ先輩…
Broadcast accident! Broadcast accident! That's bad for a debut reveal! Before I throw up, Fubuki-senpai...
はいー！いってみましょう！いただきます！
Haii! Let's go! Itadakimasu!
本当にそんな辛いのかな？
Is it really that spicy?
涙でてきた…あーでも辛いね。
Tears are coming out... Ah, but it's spicy.
あ、でも辛うま。辛うまわかりますー！辛い！
Ah, but it's spicy-delicious. I get the spicy-delicious! Spicy!
え、でも全然食べれる！バケモノ…あーでも全然辛いけど食べれる！コクがありますよね？
Eh, but I can totally eat it! Monster... Ah, but even though it's totally spicy, I can eat it! It has depth, right?
ご飯欲しくなりますねこれは
This makes me want some rice.
ヤバい、人選間違えた！人選間違えた！
Oh no, I chose the wrong people!
辛いですね〜
It's spicy~
ご飯いいんですよたぶん
Rice is good, probably.
では、子供カレー好きの
Now then, for our child-curry-loving
アキロゼ先輩どうぞ、お願いしま〜す
Aki Rosenthal-senpai, please go ahead!
あっ…はい…オッケーじゃあ
Ah... yes... Okay then,
（よくスープに）浸してね…いただきます…
Soak it well in the soup... Itadakimasu...
あっ……ちょっと喉に…！
Ah...... It just hit my throat...!
あ、今来た今来た！今来た今来た！
Ah, it's hitting me now! It's here!
くちびるに全部汁が付きました〜！
The soup got all over my lips~!
牛乳は没収しときます
I'm confiscating your milk.
ダメーー！！！私のーー！！！
Noooo!!! My milk!!!
鬼だー
You're a demon!
時間差ありますよね、時間差
There's a time lag, right? A time lag.
さあ、どんどん皆さん食べていただいて…やばい…ヨダレいっぱい出てくる…
Now, everyone eat... Oh no... My mouth is watering...
3Dお披露目でなんか言ってる…マジで痛い
Saying something during her 3D debut stream... It really hurts.
箸がでも進んでるのが
But she's still making progress with her chopsticks,
えーちゃんが…半分ぐらいもう食べました！
A-chan... has already eaten about half!
結構食べてる！え、でもラプちゃんより早く食べよ
She's eating a lot! But let's eat faster than Lap-chan!
うるさい
Shut up!
でもフブキ先輩もはやーい！
But Fubuki-senpai is fast too!
一番遅いのが、ラプラス
The slowest one is Laplus.
もう無理だって…え？これあげるよ、えーちゃん
I can't take it anymore... Eh? I'll give you this, A-chan.
あげるの、ダメだよ？ 100万円貰えなくていいのか、お前
Giving it away is not allowed! Do you not want the 1 million yen?
うっ…うっ、現金！頑張れ頑張れ！からぁーーい！！
Ugh... ugh, cash! Do your best! It's so spiiicy!!
白菜とかが凄く染みてて辛い、みたいな事前情報がありますので
We have advance info that cabbage has absorbed the flavor and is super spicy,
ぜひぜひね、白菜も食べていただいて…マジで痛い…
so please try eating the cabbage too... It really hurts...
白菜…あ、あった…やばいこれヤバイ、応援されないと食べらんない
Cabbage... Ah, found it... Oh no this is bad, I need cheering to eat.
これ10辛なんですもんね、10辛。10辛が一番辛いんですよね
This is level 10 spicy, right? Level 10 is the spiciest.
アキロゼ先輩、もう無言になってる…幹部ーー！！
Aki Rosenthal-senpai has gone completely silent... Executives!!
はい、どうしたの？
Yes, what is it?
応援して…あ、応援応援！頑張れ頑張れ！応援されないと食べらんない…あとでハンバーグ作ってあげるから
Cheer me on... Do your best! I'll make you hamburgers later!
これ飲み込む時痛くないんで…いま喋っててもいてーよ！これ
It doesn't hurt when you swallow this... You can talk while eating--ouch!
え？えーちゃんが！早い！あと…さくちぐらい…やったやったー！
Eh? A-chan is fast! And... about two more bites... Yay!
交換しよ交換しよ！ダメダメダメ！！不正不正！ 主催が不正してどうするんですか！
Let's swap, let's swap! No no no!! That's cheating! As host!
見なかったことにして！なんか……アキロゼがなんかやたら食べてるのがおかしいんだよな…
Pretend you didn't see that! It's weird that Aki Rosenthal is eating so much...
食べてます？アキさん。でもこれ美味しいから、イケるかもしれない… ズルしてるだろ絶対！
Are you eating, Aki-san? But this is delicious, so I might manage... You're cheating!
嘘じゃん！アキロゼさん我が輩に嘘ついたんだ！ 辛い、これ…辛い！この辛い！ なんかリアクションが薄いよね…？
No way! Aki-senpai lied to me! It's spicy... This is spicy! Reaction weak...?
辛い辛い。アキロゼさんさ、ちょっとさ、もし辛かったらどうするの？
Spicy. Aki Rosenthal-senpai, if it's spicy, what do you do?
辛かったらどうする？なんか見た目どんな感じ？見た目見せろよ！おーい！！やめろよ！ お前、明らかに茶色いだろこれ！
What do you do? What does it look like? Show us! Hey!! Stop it! It's brown!
ちょ、我が輩の見てよ！まっ赤！まっ赤だよ！ うそ、うそ、うそ、うそ…
Look at mine! It's totally red! No way, no way...
全然ちげーだろうが！え！？嘘！？キムチとカレーぐらい差あるけど！！ 本当だよアキちゃん、全然違うじゃん！
They're completely different! Kimchi and curry are worlds apart! Aki-chan, totally!
アキちゃんそれ激辛？ホントに？あれ？ ちょっとじゃあ味が気になると思いますので
Aki-chan, is that super spicy? Really? Well, you're probably curious about the taste,
同じのを用意させていただきましたのでじゃあこれちょっとラプ食べてもらって
so we prepared the exact same thing, let's have Laplus eat this one.
色どうですか、色？アキロコにさ、なんか茶色いね 茶色いよほら、みて
How's the color? It looks kind of brown. Brown... look, see?
えー！！これ別物じゃないですか！別物やんけ！ では、食べてください
Ehh!! This is a completely different thing! It's totally different! Eat up.
なにこれ？ いやいやいや！辛い辛い辛い！辛かったよ！どうですか？お味は
What is this? No no no! Spicy! It was spicy! How's the taste?
ただの豆腐やん！美味しい豆腐 嘘だって〜
It's just tofu! Delicious tofu. Just kidding~
アキロゼさんさ、アキロゼ先輩ちょっとなんか普通のお鍋が用意されちゃったみたいなので 他の3人と同じお鍋を用意させていただきましたのでこちら
Aki-senpai, a regular hot pot was prepared by mistake, so we prepared the same one.
ひとりだけ別の食ってたんだげどー！
She was eating a completely different one by herself!
明らかに色が違うね 先ほど「同じ」って言っていたので 多分パクパクね、食べれると思いますのでぜひぜひパクパクと食べていただければなと思います
The colors are different. Since you said "same", you can eat it up!
そうですよ！ひとくちじゃだめですよ！ 白菜の部分食べてください 白菜の部分！ ちゃんとね！ちゃんとね！ あ、それ美味しそう
That's right! Eat the cabbage part! Properly! Ah, that looks good.
もつもつ…ちょっと後からくるんでね、ぜひぜひ。じゃあ、いただきます
It comes after a delay. Well then, itadakimasu.
震えてるw 震えてる。顔、顔！
She's shaking lol She's shaking. Her face!
結構すぐ来た！辛い！あ、結構すぐ来た！
It hit pretty fast! It's spicy! Ah, it hit fast!
ヤバい辛い！！ヤバいヤバい！ 牛乳牛乳！踊り出した、踊り出した
So spicy!! Oh no! Milk milk! She started dancing!
この苦しみが分かったか！アキロゼさん！ホンマや…
Do you understand this suffering now, Aki-senpai! True...
（これを）ずっと食ってた！！ね！ほら！ね！言ったでしょ？ 我が輩、我が輩だけ”普通の人”なの！！普通の人はこうなの！
She's been eating this the whole time!! I'm the only normal one here!
ということで100万円は誰の手に渡るのでしょうか？
So, whose hands will the 1 million yen end up in?
でも、えーちゃんってこと？どっちが速かったかな？ えーちゃんとフブキ先輩 どちらになるのでしょうか！？発表お願いします！
A-chan and Fubuki-senpai... Which will it be?! Please announce!
誰が100万円なんて言った？
Who said anything about 1 million yen?
あんなのは嘘だ！
That was a lie!
100万円なんて無いいーー！！
There is no 1 million yen!!
引っかかったーー！！！
You fell for it!!!
ざこざこざこざこざこざこばかーー！！！！
Loser, loser, loser, loser, idiot!!!!
なんだとぉ！！
What was that?!
辛いもの食べただけだよお前らは！
You guys just ate something spicy!
いやでも美味しいもの食べさせてもらったってことかじゃあ
Well, but that means you got to eat something delicious, then.
反応が違うなぁ...
Your reaction is different...
まあ、ラプラスさん出禁ですね！今日から
Well, Laplus-san, you're banned! Starting today.
なんと！！
No way!!
すいませーん、じゃあ出禁で！
Sorry, then I'm banned!
私はラプラスに言わされてただけなので
I was just made to say that by Laplus, so...
裏切るのか！！
You're betraying me?!
許してくださーい
Please forgive meeee!
じゃあルイさんしょうがないか！
Well, I guess we have no choice, Lui-san!
じゃあ100万円はあげないですけど、バケモンっていう称号はあげます
Well, I won't give you 1 million yen, but I'll give you the title of "monster".
バケモン！？
A monster?!
うれしいのかな……
I wonder if that makes me happy...
嬉しくないよ、やだよそんな称号……
I'm not happy, I don't want a title like that...
じゃあ激辛三姉妹で、頑張りましょうね
Well, let's do our best as the super spicy trio!
なんかやりたいですね！
We want to do something!
本当に？
Really?
そうだよ！
That's right!
がんばろ〜
Let's do our best~
やってらんねーよ！こんなの！
I can't deal with this! Stuff like this!
それでは以上、ホロライブ激辛選手権でした〜
And with that, the Hololive Super Spicy Championship has concluded~
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!
二度とやるか！ばいばーい！
I'm never doing this again! Bye-bye!
ほら食べ終わんないと帰れないんですよ
Look, we can't go home until we finish eating.
そうだ
That's right.
巻いてお願いしまーす！巻いて巻いて！
Wrap it up, please! Wrap it up, wrap it up!
もう食べらんないよ
I can't eat anymore.
食べてたでしょ
You were eating.
食べてない
I wasn't.
食べて食べて、巻いて巻いて！
Eat, eat, wrap it, wrap it!
じゃああとは我々食べるとして、じゃああとひと口、あと最後の一口ってこうか
Well then, assuming the rest of us eat, then how about one more bite, just one last bite...
どうぞ！
Go ahead!
どうぞぞぞ！
Go, go, go!
せーの
Ready, set,
いただきまーす！いただきます！
Itadakimasu! Itadakimasu!
なんだこれー！辛い！なんだこれー！やってやるー！
What is this?! It's spicy! What is this?! I'll do it!
ちょっと待って！嘘でしょ、戻って帰ってそのままで
Wait a minute! No way, go back and stay like that!
もうだめだ
I'm done for.
女だらけの！王様ゲーム〜！
An all-girls' King Game~!
イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
よろしいよろしい
Very well, very well.
はい！じゃあ自己紹介するぞ〜
Alright! Now let's do introductions~
冠もぐせよ〜
Put on your crown~
ラプラス・ダークネスでーすよろしくお願いしまーす
I'm Laplus Darknesss, nice to meet you!
適当だな〜
So casual~
そうだな〜
That's right~
ばっくばっくばく〜んどうも〜！秘密結社holoxの掃除屋でインターンシャチの沙花叉クロヱでーす！お邪魔しまーす！
Bak bak bak~un, hello~! Secret society holoX's cleaner and intern, orca Sakamata Chloe! Pardon the interruption!
皆さんこんまっする〜！ホロライブ3期生の、うーん、脳筋、白銀ノエルでーす！よろしくお願いします！
Hello muscle everyone~! Hololive 3rd gen's, um, muscle brain, Shirogane Noel! Nice to meet you!
はーいこんやっぴー！ホロライブ4期生の常闇トワ様でーす！本物だ！もうこんな感じです…
Hiii kon-yappy! Hololive 4th gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama! The real deal! This is how it is...
こんねね〜！ホロライブ5期生、トワ様とラブラブな桃鈴ねねでーす！
Kon-nene~! Hololive 5th gen, Momosuzu Nene who is lovey-dovey with Towa-sama!
やめろー！
Cut it out!
脳が破壊されちまう…
My brain is gonna get destroyed...
なんでだよ！よろしく〜
Why?! Nice to meet you~
おかしいだろ！
That's weird!
始まった
It started.
ということでですね、今回この5人で王様ゲームやりたいと思しまーす！
And so, this time we want to play the King Game with these 5 people!
なんで呼ばれたの〜？
Why were we called here~?
なんか分かんに〜！
I don't know~!
なんか？まあ下心と……あの下心と！
What? Well, ulterior motives... and that ulterior motive!
下心とちょっとなんか面白いかな、と思うメンツを集めて王様ゲームやらせようと思って。
Ulterior motives and gathering members I thought would be fun to make play the King Game.
王様ゲーム、やったことある人いますか？
Has anyone here ever played the King Game?
やったことはないけど、BL漫画でよく読んでるから詳しい。知識だけはめっちゃある。
I haven't played it, but I read BL manga a lot so I'm well-versed. I have tons of knowledge, at least.
欲望じゃねーか…
That's just desire...
まあね、王様ゲームよ、我輩言ってる我輩やったことないんですけどね！
Well, you see, the King Game, though I—as I say, I've never actually played it!
今回、初体験王様ゲームなんでね、ちょっと…
Since this is my first time experiencing the King Game, um...
いやでもラプラス以外が王様引けば勝ちみたいなとこあるからね
Well, but if anyone other than Laplus draws the King, it's kind of a win, right?
なんで！みんなで引きましょう！頑張って！
Why?! Let's all draw! Do your best!
王様になりたい！むしろ
I want to be the King! Rather,
安全地帯に逃げる気ですね？
You're planning to run to the safe zone, aren't you?
我輩なりたい！王様なりたい！沙花叉もやりたい！
I want to be! I want to be the King! Sakamata wants to do it!
愛と欲望のまぎれでこの王様ゲームを制するのは誰だ
Who will conquer this King Game amidst love and desire?
マジでやりたくね〜！おいおいおいおい！
I really don't want to do this~! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
やるぞ〜
Let's do this~
せーの、王様だーれ！
Ready, set, who's the King!
はい！
Hii!
ちょっとじゃあ見せて……なに？なに？ちょっと……なるほどね！
Let's see then... What? What? Wait... I see!
王様誰ですか！王様は……
Who is the King?! The King is...
ねねーー！！やばいやばいやばい！マジで！ねね先輩か〜
Nene~~!! No no no no! Seriously! Nene-senpai~
じゃあ……2番の人が……2番の人が？
Then... person number 2... person number 2?
今からねね真ん中に立つから、ねねに愛の告白……してよね〜！
From now on, Nene is going to stand in the middle, so a confession of love to Nene... You better do it~!
自分が得しようとしてる！
You're trying to benefit yourself!
じゃあちょっと2番の人手上げて。はい我輩です！！
Well, raise your hand if you're number 2. Yes, it's me!!
うわぁあああ！！ふざけんなよ〜！ナイス！
Wuaaaaaah!! Are you kidding me~! Nice!
え〜愛の告白〜？
Eee~ a confession of love~?
じゃあ行きますよ？辛いチキン食べたから息臭かったらごめん…
Well, here I go? I ate spicy chicken so sorry if my breath smells...
愛の告白まで……3…2…1…ねね、愛してるZE！
Up to the confession of love... 3... 2... 1... Nene, I love you ZE!
失笑やめて…浅い！浅いなぁ〜
Stop snickering... Shallow! So shallow~
何か違うなぁ〜浅い！
That's somehow different~ Shallow!
あ、まだやれますよ！外野うるさいんだけど！！まだやれます！
Ah, I can still do it! The outsiders are so noisy!! I can still do it!
ちょっと今の浅かった！浅いってなんだよ…ちょっと待ってよ
That was a bit shallow! What do you mean shallow... wait a minute.
ねね…好きだよ…
Nene... I love you...
まっきー！やめた方がいいよ〜
Makkii! You better stop~
なんかちがーう！照れを感じるな〜？
That's not it! I can sense some shyness, huh~?
バックハグからの告白でいいすか？じゃあ
A confession via back hug, is that okay? Alright then,
あ、すごいやってくれるじゃん
Oh, you're really going for it!
めちゃやってくれーる！
She's totally doing it!
行きますよ？
Here I go?
…ねね！！
...Nene!!
あー！できさがない！あーーっ！！
Aah! No way, no way! Aaaaaah!!
ラブ様が3Dになってやりたかったことこれかよ！！
Is this what Lap-sama wanted to do in 3D?!
違う！逆だろ！我輩は！！なんで吾輩がやらなきゃいけねぇんだよー！！
No! It's the other way around! Why do *I* have to do this?!
いい気分だったな〜
That felt pretty good~
なんか普通にやけどを負っただけだった…
It just felt like I got burnt normally...
まぁ見てるこっちも結構やけどしたけどね
Well, we were watching and got pretty burnt too.
ホントだよー…見ないでっ！！
Seriously... Don't look!!
採点するとしたら何点？今の
If you had to score it, what would it be?
え、今の告白ですかぁ？
Eh, that confession?
いや100点だろふざけんな
No, 100 points, are you kidding me?
え、2点
Eh, 2 points.
ふざけんなよ！！じゃあお前やってみろよ！吾輩に！
Are you kidding me!! Then you try doing it! To me!
バカ！王様ゲームのルール分かれよ！
Idiot! Understand the rules of the King Game!
違う！イヤダヤダヤダ！やってみろよ！！！
No! No way, no way! Try doing it!!!
いや、ダメダメダメ、吾輩がルールだから
No, no, no, because I'm the rules--
ラプラス…好きだよ。
Laplus... I love you.
あ、そういうのが欲しかった！
Ah, that's what I wanted!
これだよ欲しかったのは！
This is what I wanted!
王様ゲーム破綻してるだろが！
The King Game is completely broken!
なんでやられたんだよ！ありがとねー
Why did you accept it! Thanks~
ってことは今見本見せてもらったからさ〜？
So since we just got shown an example~?
なんで！もういいよ！！！
Why! Enough already!!!
そうですね〜！！ちょっと本物見たいな〜
That's right~~! I kinda wanna see the real deal~
ちょっと1回だけガチなの行こうよ、ガチなの
Let's just do a serious one for once, a real one.
いやもういいって…
No, enough already...
王様やぞ！王様やぞ！！
You're the king! You're the king!!
うるせぇ！黙れ！！
Shut up! Be quiet!!
ねねさん…好きだよ。
Nene-san... I love you.
ああっ！いいじゃん！
Aah! That's good!
出来るじゃん！やれば〜
You can do it! When you try~
良く出来まちた〜！良く出来ま……
Well done~ Well do...
うるさーい！もういいんだよ…！！！
Shut up! Enough already...!!!
ねぇ我輩の企画なのにまだ得してることひとつもない…
Hey, it's my project, but I haven't profited at all...
まだ始まったばっかやぞ！もう早く次次次〜！！
It just started! Hurry up, next, next, next~~!
せーの！王様だーれ！
Ready, set! Who's the king?!
なんだよっ！ひとりおかしい人いるー！
What the heck! There's one weird person here!
やばいねるやばいねる、絶対そうだって〜
Neru's in trouble, it's definitely that one~
おう、わかりやすいなー
Oh, very obvious~
やーだー！！
No way!!
じゃあ…いいですか、皆さん？粛々にお願いしますね？
Now... is that okay, everyone? Please be quiet and orderly, okay?
うわうわ、なんかもうわかりやすいなー
Wow wow, somehow it's so obvious~
じゃあちょっとあの…王様ですか
So, um... are you the king?
はーいはいはーい！吾輩でーす！！王様吾輩でーす！皆さん、はい！
Hiiii! It's me!! The king is me! Everyone, yes!
媚びタイムお願いしま〜す
Flattery time, please~
ちょっとこれマジで運ゲーなんですけど
Wait, this is seriously RNG, but
ちょ我輩はこの4択を外すわけにはいかないんだよね…
I can't afford to miss these 4 choices...
いや〜ちょっと当てようとしてない！？
No~ aren't you trying to guess it?!
マジ欲が出てるわ〜！
You're being too greedy!
ねぇ怖い怖い！選ぼうとしてるよね！？本当に当てないでくれ！！
Hey, scary scary! You're trying to pick, right?! Really don't guess it!!
一回だけ…一回だけちょっと開示してもらって…
Just once... just once let me reveal...
お前ルールをぐちゃぐちゃにするなよ！
Don't mess up the rules!
ちょ2番だった人だけ…
Just the person who was number 2...
ちょ、ノエルさんノエルさん…
Noel-san, Noel-san...
あっこれね、OK OK…
Ah this, OK OK...
2択になった、2択になった…さあさあさあ2択だ！
It's down to 2 choices... Come on, it's 50/50!
この2択を外すわけにはいかない…がんばれ〜
I can't miss these 2 choices... Do your best~
王様と……3番手が手を繋ぐ！！で散歩する！
The King and... number 3 hold hands!! And go for a walk!
どっちだ！どっちなんだ！？3番の人は手を上げてください！
Which is it! Which is it?! Number 3, please raise your hand!
うえええええええええい！！！！！
Ueeeeeei!!!!!
よっしゃらーー！！
Yesss!!
よっしゃ！やったぞ！
Yatta! We did it!
キモいだろこれ！！
Isn't this creepy!!
今日これだけの用にこの回をやったまである
We practically did this episode just for this today.
これで完全に王様ゲームの…やったーー！！
With this, completely the King Game... Yay!!
じゃあこの事務所ちょっと手を繋いでもら…手、ちょまって…消毒しようかな、一旦
So let's have this agency hold hands... wait... let's disinfect first.
ねぇキモい！！いいよ早くやれって…
Hey, creepy! Fine, just do it already...
え…チョット……
Eh... wait...
ねぇ、キモいキモい なんかニヤニヤしてる…
Hey, creepy creepy, you're smirking...
変な空気 かわいそうだろ3人がおめー！！
Weird atmosphere, aren't those three pitiful, you guys!!
いやいやちょっと恥ずかしいだろ！
No no, it's embarrassing!
3人どうでもいいんで！
Those three don't matter!
おいおいおいどうでもいいとか言うな！！
Hey hey hey, don't say they don't matter!!
デ…デートですね…
It's... a date...
何見せられてんのマジで〜？
What on earth are we being made to watch~?
今日この後どうします？
What are we doing after this today?
え、この後一直線で帰るかな
Uh, I guess I'll head straight home after this.
ツノが痛い！
My horn hurts!
ツノがさ、刺さってるから！
Because your horn is poking in!
こ…こうやって歩きます！！
W-We'll walk like this!!
え…ちょ…幸せですね！！幸せですね！！！
Eh... w-wait... this is happiness!! This is happiness!!!
ああ良かったねえ良かったねえ〜
Aah, I'm so glad for you~
あぁ〜…トワさまぁ…！！
Aah... Towa-sama...!!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ツノが！ツノが凄いんだよ！！
The horns! The horns are intense!!
もうコレで満足ですか……
Are you satisfied with just this......
皆さん、我輩たち今日幸せになります！
Everyone, we are going to be happy today!
「吾輩たち」じゃない！「吾輩」だけだろ！
Not "we"! Just "me"!
このツノがやっぱり、鋭利でちょっと危ないね
These horns are sharp and a bit dangerous, after all.
はい、よしよし…
Yes, yoshi yoshi...
あ！よしよししてもらえてたよ！いま！
Ah! I was getting petted! Just now!
あぁもう！よしよし、はいはい
Aah geez! Yoshi yoshi, yes yes.
ありがとうございます！！
Thank you very much!!
ちょありがとうみんな！
Hey thanks everyone!
よしよし〜よく頑張ったな！
Yoshi yoshi~ You did your best!
オイオイオイダメ！！ふざけんな！おい！！
Oi oi oi no!! Are you kidding me! Oi!!
ダメ！だめっすよちょっと！！
No! You can't do that, wait!!
そんなん許されませんからね！
You can't get away with that!
はあー、キツかった
Whew, that was rough.
これさごめんね？みんなどこの時間
Sorry about this everyone, this time—
いやもう、気持ちよかったっす！！
No, it felt great!!
はいっ！じゃあ満足したんで次！
Alright! Then since we're satisfied, next!
ご褒美タイムじゃん〜次いっすよ！もうなんかもういっすよ！
It's reward time~ Next is fine! Anything is fine now!
なんでもやれます 今我輩〜
I can do anything right now, me~
うんなんでもやりますよ、行きましょう〜！
Yup, we can do anything, let's go~!
もうアツアツなの見せられたな…
We really got shown something lovey-dovey...
あ、あ、あ、集まって！
A, a, a, gather around!
行きましょう！せーの！王様だーれ！
Let's go! Ready, set! Who's the king?!
なんだよっ！なになどなになど
What the heck! What's this, what's this
じゃあちょ…本物の王様だーれ？ですか！
So, um... who's the real king? Is that it!
っしゃあああああああ!!!
Yesss!
トワ先輩!?
Towa-senpai!?
えー、じゃあ…1番と、3番と、4番が「hololive」という文字を体でつくる
Um, well... Numbers 1, 3, and 4 will form the word "hololive" with their bodies.
はいじゃあ1番の人？
Okay, who's number 1?
はーい！我輩でーす！
Hi! That's me!
あ、3番の人？
Ah, who's number 3?
はーい！ねね～
Hi! Nene~
はい、4番の人？
Yes, who's number 4?
マジで！？
Seriously!?
なんか回避する能力つけてる？
Do you have some evasion ability?
居るだけのひとになってる…
You're just someone who's just standing there...
何か変なもの見せられて可哀そうですよね！？
Isn't it pitiful they have to watch something weird!?
ガチオーディエンスだったね！
They were a real audience!
帰っていいですか！？
Can I go home!?
ダメダメダメ！ここから！
No no no! From here!
さすがに3人言えばさ、入ってくるかなと思って
I figured if three people said it, they'd join in...
え、3人でアルファベット8文字…個ずつやってく？
Um, 3 people for 8 letters of the alphabet... doing them one by one?
「H」は簡単じゃないすか？だって。3人で「H」を作るっていう。
"H" isn't easy, right? I mean, the three of them make an "H".
はい、じゃあラプラス、浮けば？
Okay, then Laplus, if you float?
「浮けば？」ってヤバいよ。
"If you float?" That's bad.
そんな、浮けねえよ。
There's no way I can float.
あーなるほどね！早く！
Ah, I see! Hurry!
「hololive」の「H」！
The "H" in "hololive"!
おー！オッケーオッケー！ナイス！
Oh! Okay okay! Nice!
次、2人で…次2人で、あのこうやってやってください。こうやって。
Next, two people... Next two people, do it like this. Like this.
団長不安だな～ｗ
Danchou's looking worried~ lol
あ、いい感じ！いい感じ！
Ah, good feel! Good feel!
「hololive」の「O」！
The "O" in "hololive"!
じゃあ我輩が寝るんで、ちょっとあの…縦地誰かやってください。
Well, since I'm going to lie down, someone do the vertical bar.
「hololive」の「L」！
The "L" in "hololive"!
次もっかい「O」やらない？
Shouldn't we do "O" one more time?
「hololive」の「O」！
The "O" in "hololive"!
じゃあ次「L」なんで誰か寝てください。
Then next is "L", so someone lie down.
「hololive」の「L」！
The "L" in "hololive"!
え、「V」ちょっとムズくないっすか？
Um, isn't "V" a bit difficult?
体感鍛えよう。
Train your core.
「hololive」の「V」！
The "V" in "hololive"!
え、「E」？え、ムズくないっすか「E」…？
Um, "E"? Um, isn't "E" difficult...?
あ、いけてるいけてる！
Ah, it's working, it's working!
ラプラスがフォークだから難しいけど…ほら、いける！
Laplus is a fork so it's hard, but... look, you can do it!
いける！
You can do it!
「hololive」の「E」！
The "E" in "hololive"!
何？なんか達成感あるの悔しいっすね。
What? It's frustrating that there's a sense of accomplishment.
謎の達成感ありましたよ。
There was a mysterious sense of accomplishment.
トワ様これしたかったの？
Was this what Towa-sama wanted to do?
トワはなんかホロライブらしいなと思いましたけどね。
Towa thought it felt very Hololive, though.
いやーそうですね、なんか「何見せられてんだろ」は常にあるんですけど、でもいい感じでした！
Yeah, that's right, there's always that "what am I being made to watch" feeling, but it felt good!
絆感じましたよ。
I felt a bond.
なんか一致団結感はあった。やったぁ！！
There was a sense of unity. Yay!!
「王様ゲーム」……？次誰かクロヱ、指さないと…
"King Game" ...? Next, someone has to point at Chloe...
クロヱ指さないと！そーだよぉ…！
Got to point at Chloe! That's right...!
凄い回避能力があるって！
Saying she has amazing evasion ability!
でもこのまま帰ってもいいなって思ってて…
Though I thought it'd be fine just going home like this...
だめだめだめ！！！なんでだよ！
No no no no! Why?!
いや見るだけ見てちょっと帰ろっかなって…
I mean just watching a bit and going home...
じゃあお前ここに居なくていいだろうがよ！
Then you don't need to be here!
せーの、大阪だーれ！はい！
Ready, set, who's the king! Hi!
王様誰ですか！はーい！
Who is the king! Hi!
2連続！またトワになっちゃったー☆
Two in a row! It became Towa again☆
あ、王様権譲っていただいても全然…いいですよ？
Ah, it's totally... fine if you hand over the king's authority?
じゃあ、王様権譲ってもよくて、
Well, I can hand over the king's authority,
でも自分もなんかしなきゃいけないやつにしてくれるんだったらいいよ？いいですよ？
but is it okay if you make it something where I also have to do something? It's fine?
1番が…沙花叉を踏んだくれる…これどうですか？
Number 1 steps on Sakamata... How is this?
キモい…
Creepy...
どうですかコレ？
How is this?
え、誰ですか1番！！！！ちょっと気になるなー！！！
Eh, who is number 1?! I'm kind of curious~!
みんな気になるよね～？誰、だれだれ～？
Everyone's curious, right? Who, who is it~?
1番の方ー！あ！やったーー！！
Number 1! Ah! Yayyy!!
お前の趣味やんけ！
That's just your hobby!
おかしいだろ！
That's weird!
早い早い早いよ！やばいでしょ！
Too fast, too fast, too fast! That's dangerous!
え、ちょっと…どうぞどうぞ？踏んでください？
Eh, um... go ahead, go ahead? Please step on me?
じゃあ、行きます！
Then, here I go!
オラてめえ踏んづけんだよ！
I'm gonna trample you, damn it!
コノヤロ！！シャチ野郎がよ！
You bastard!! You orca bastard!
エッチな3Dしゃがってよ！お前！
Doing an ecchi 3D! You!
エッチなエロライブが始まってしまっただろうがよ！コノヤロ！！
An ecchi lewd live has started, hasn't it, damn it!! You bastard!!
おらおらおらおら！
Take that take that take that take that!
ありがとうございます！！
Thank you!!
出来れば、仰向けも欲しいです～…
If possible, I'd also like you to face up~...
いいってもう！
Enough already!
出来れば仰向けも欲しいです～
If possible, I'd also like you to face up~
いやでもこれはさ、他にも番号いますからね？
No but this, there are other numbers too, right?
確かに！それもあるね！
True! That's also true!
だから仰向けをね……
So facing up...
沙花叉、王様だもん！え、いいですよね？？
Sakamata is the king! Eh, that's fine, right??
いやこれダメですね
No this is no good
元々の王様の権限はトワ株主だから
the original king's authority is Towa-shareholder so
お前さー！自分で自分にやればいいじゃん！
Youー! Just do it to yourself!
北海道にね！自分で自分にののしればいい
In Hokkaido! Insulting yourself...
いやだよつまんないじゃん…
No way, that's boring...
いつもの話じゃん…ねえ！
It's the usual story... Hey!
いつもの話！
The usual story!
え、あの王様…なんですけど…あの、踏んでもらいたいんですけど！
Um, that king... is... Um, I want you to step on me!
すいませーん！
Excuse me!
なんで…？なんで…！？
Why...? Why...-?!
こいつほっといてみんなでお昼ご飯食べに行きましょうよ！
Let's leave this guy alone and go eat lunch everyone!
いいないいな！行こ行こ！！ひどいー！！
Sounds great! Let's go!! So mean!!
もう満足したよね？
You're satisfied already, right?
もう満足しましたよ！
I'm already satisfied!
もう！満足！楽しかった～！
Already! Satisfied! It was fun~!
いやちょっと待って待って待って待って！違うよね？
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! That's wrong, right?
やだー！！！やだー！！！
Noooo!!! Noooo!!!
なんで、ひどい！ひどい、かえらないで！！
Why, how mean! How mean, don't go back!!
なんで、ひどい！ひどい、かえんでい！！
Why, how cruel! Cruel, don't go!
やだやだやだ…やだー…
No, no, no... no...
ひどい…
Cruel...
助けてくださ～い…
Help meee...
え～ん…
Waaah...
え、ほんとに踏んでくれないんですか？
Eh, are you really not going to step on me?
あなたがねがった 幸せなと
The happiness you wished for...
あたりまえのような ものだけれど
is something so ordinary,
どこにもないよと あなたはいう
yet you say it's nowhere to be found.
そんな世界が また始まる
Such a world begins once again.
例えば、今此処に置かれた花に
For instance, to the flower placed right here,
知らぬ間に手を合わせる
hands are put together unconsciously.
僕には分かるのだろう
I wonder if I will understand.
こんな世界は沈んでゆく
Such a world is sinking away.
今日も電車は遅れている
Today, too, the train is running late.
僕の予定など知りもせずに
Without knowing a thing about my schedule,
悪びれを一つ二つ飲み込んで
swallowing one or two excuses without remorse,
空に咲く雲とか笑っている
the clouds blooming in the sky are smiling.
楽しそうに次ぎ散ってゆくよ
Happily scattering away one after another,
どうまとの中へ 積み上げた思い出
Into the heart of the city, piling up memories,
ひとつどこにもならない旅立つ
setting off on a journey with nowhere to belong.
あなたへの下駄の中
Inside the geta for you...
今日も変わらず 世界は回る
Today, too, the world keeps spinning unchangingly.
いぬのすきまから 顔を覗く
Peeking out from the gap of the fence,
おテント様が 照らしている
the sun is shining down.
悲しそうに勝手に ゆられながら
Swaying sorrowfully on its own,
道行く人は 通り過ぎてく
people walking down the street pass by.
あなたが どれだけの痛みを抱え
How much pain you must be carrying,
悩んで 苦しんだのか
worrying and suffering through—
例えば 今ここに置かれた花に
For instance, to the flower placed right here,
知らなしなくて 手を合わせる
unwittingly putting our hands together.
僕には 分かるのだろう
I wonder if I will understand.
あなたが どれだけの痛みを抱え
How much pain you were carrying,
悩んで 苦しんだのか
worrying and suffering through—
知らじらしくて 手を合わせる
feigning ignorance as we put our hands together,
あなたがねがった 幸せなと
The happiness you wished for...
あたりまえのような ものだけれど
is something so ordinary,
どこにもないよと あなたはいう
yet you say it's nowhere to be found.
そんな世界が 沈んでゆく
Such a world is sinking away.
例えば、今此処に置かれた花に
For example, to a flower placed in this day's place...
世界は変わらず
the world remains unchanged.
まわる
Spun around,
spun around.
…
...
えー
Ah...
ここまで見てくれて、みんなありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much for watching up to here!
次で最後の曲になります。
Next will be our final song.
オリジナルの方を考えたので、注目してください。
I've thought of original choreography for it, so please look forward to it!
その分頑張って踊るので、見てください！
So please look forward to it, as I'll do my best dancing!
それでは、最後の曲、合縁事変です！
Now then, for our final song, it's "Ai-en Jihen"!
Can you feel "Madness"?
この世界の全て
All of this world,
Can you feel "Galaxy"?
果てを飛び越えた
flying past the limits,
Glory
バイアスかかるバイブスで深淵より宿すパワーをtune up
Tune up the power dwelling deep within with biased vibes,
Massで成り立つCapitalに一罰百戒　穿つ「理想像」
piercing the "ideal" with a hundred-fold punishment on the capital of mass.
傷天害理　汝、二乗で満たす存在意義　In the Flow　否な「ない」返し「はい」
In the Flow, with undeniable returning answers,
獅子搏兎 + Impact!　まわりまわる多様性を
Lion's prowess + Impact! Binding all around diversity
感情的なルールで縛り付け　「うるせえ全く！」
with emotional rules, saying "Shut up already!"
うねりうねる可能性で　全て超えたIdentity
surpassing everything with twisting, winding possibilities—Identity.
Can you feel my soul?
Baby, up & up now
3, 2, 1
Nothing bad happened.
案じたってまわる循環定義
With cyclic definition while expecting the worst,
変わらぬ真理　合縁奇縁の淀み点　make it
make it unchanged truth, fateful gathering, and the vortex of fate.
Nothing bad happened.
君は君　いらぬ疑心暗鬼
You are you, unwanted suspicious demons,
不毛なBlowと焦らすFlow　疼く鼓動でHigh!
barren blows, scorching flows, and throbbing heartbeats—High!
up & up
Up and up,
我が道をゆくMinority　あざどくIrony
walking my own path, minority, sassy irony,
ちらり見せるピュアなハート　惨殺御免
showing a glimpse of a pure heart, ready for murder.
夢描いてた名声赫々　人類学　核心にtuning up　すべて解き明かす
Unraveling all of humanity's core with tuning up,
心満たす様　その美的知識を刺激して　私的に生きてる体も shaking up and shape up
shaking up and shape up, living my own life with aesthetic knowledge stimulating,
我が道をゆく共犯者
walking my own path, accomplices.
Are you ready to fall into deep?
かすむ視界は銘々　響く名声　叫べ「メーデー」
Sights blurred, echoes clear, shouting "Mayday!"
無垢な犠牲　足りない愛を狂わす
innocent sacrifice, driving unrequited love mad.
まわりまわる多様性を　感情的なルールで縛り付け　「うるせえ全く！」　うねりうねる可能性で　全て超えたIdentity
Surpassing everything with twisting, winding possibilities—Identity.
Can you feel my soul?
Baby, up & up now
3, 2, 1
Nothing bad happened.
案じたってまわる循環定義
With cyclic definition while expecting the worst,
変わらぬ真理　合縁奇縁の淀み点　make it
make it unchanged truth, fateful gathering, and the vortex of fate.
Nothing bad happened.
君は君　いらぬ疑心暗鬼
You are you, unwanted suspicious demons,
不毛なBlowと焦らすFlow　疼く鼓動でHigh!
barren blows, scorching flows, and throbbing heartbeats—High!
up & up up & up
Up and up, up and up...
告知
[Announcement]
風真いろは 3Dお披露目
[Kazama Iroha 3D Debut]
沙花叉クロヱ 3Dお披露目
[Sakamata Chloe 3D Debut]
博衣こより 3Dお披露目
[Hakui Koyori 3D Debut]
鷹嶺ルイ 3Dお披露目
[Takane Lui 3D Debut]
ラプラス・ダークネス 3Dお披露目
[Laplus Darkness 3D Debut]
そして
And then...
3Dアジトお披露目
[holoX 3D Hideout Reveal]
holoX、集合。
holoX Assembled.
刮目せよ！
Behold!